A Guide to the Edward L. Stone/Borderland Coal Company Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Borderland Coal Co. Papers
  - Virginia Bridge & Iron Co. correspondence, 1904 -1914 (Box Box 332)
  - G. W. Taylor - correspondence, 1904 -1910 (Box Box 332)
  - Vulcan Coal Co. - balance sheets and other financial records; correspondence, 1913 -1915; (2 folders) (Box Box 332)
  - James P. Woods - correspondence, 1907 -1915 (Box Box 332)
  - Borderland Coal Co. - Operation #1 balance sheets, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 334)
  - Borderland Coal Co. - Operation #2 balance sheets, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 334)
  - Agreements - Borderland Coal business, 1909 -1914 (Box Box 334)
  - Applications for work with Borderland Coal Co., 1908 -1914 (Box Box 334)
  - Bailey Property Co. - correspondence regarding coal properties, 1908 -1915 (Box Box 334)
  - L. E. Armentrout - Manager - information on secret service agents tracing union organizers; correspondence, 1914 -1915; (2 folders) (Box Box 334)
  - Ernest B. Fishburn - secretary-treasurer of Borderland Coal Co., 1909 -1915 (Box Box 336)
  - James D. Francis - correspondence, 1910 -1914 (Box Box 336)
  - Fuel contracts, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 336)
  - Goodman Mfg. Co.- coal mining machines and equipment, 1908 -1913 (Box Box 336)
  - Edwards & Bradford Lumber Co. - correspondence, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 336)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", 1910 -1915 (Box Box 336)
  - F. T. Lee - coal related correspondence relating to Johnson Coal Co., 1909 -1910 (Box Box 341)
  - Leschen & Sons Rope Co. - correspondence concerning track rope for Borderland Coal tramway, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 341)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, including F. H. LaBaume, Thomas S. Martin, W. A. Peake, W. P. Murray, 1907 -1911 (Box Box 341)
  - Borderland Coal Co. booklets - excellent description of Borderland Coal Co. to layman in pamphlet form, written by E. L. Stone for purpose of advertising, 1914; (2 folders) (Box Box 343)
  - Borderland Coal Sales Co. - financial reports and correspondence, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 343)
  - S. R. Brame - correspondence, 1904 -1912 (Box Box 343)
  - Car Allotment Commission, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 343)
  - Borderland Coal Co., West Virginia -correspondence and copy of by-laws of the company, 1910 -1914 (Box Box 343)
  - Daily reports, 1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 346)
  - Annual report of the president - Stone to stockholders of Borderland Coal, 1908 -1911 (Box Box 346)
  - L. E. Armentrout - Borderland Coal correspondence between Stone and Armentrout, 1912 -1913; (2 folders) (Box Box 346)
  - Borderland Coal monthly statements operation #1, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 348)
  - Borderland Coal monthly statements operation #2, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 348)
  - Operation sheet - Borderland Coal Sales Co., 1914 -1915 (Box Box 348)
  - Plant #1 - Borderland, 1911 (Box Box 348)
  - Plant #2 - Armen, 1915 (Box Box 348)
  - Notice of meetings, 1911 (Box Box 348)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Washer, 1911 (Box Box 348)
  - Statements - Borderland Coal Sales Co., 1911 -1915 (Box Box 351)
  - Miss C. Rankin - secretary and treasurer of Borderland Coal Sales Co., 1913 -1915 (Box Box 351)
  - Public Service Commission - coal operations, 1913 (Box Box 351)
  - Edward L. Stone - correspondence, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 351)
  - John A. Roebling's Sons Co. - correspondence, 1907 -1910 (Box Box 351)
  - D. E. Spangler - correspondence, 1907 -1915 (Box Box 351)
  - E. R. Johnson - correspondence, 1909 -1913; (4 folders) (Box Box 355)
  - Report of secretary and treasurer financial reports, 1907 -1912 (Box Box 359)
  - Daily reports, 1914; (2 folders) (Box Box 359)
  - E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., 1908 (Box Box 362)
  - Daily reports, 1908 -1909; (3 folders) (Box Box 364)
  - Monthly reports - financial statements for Borderland Coal Co., 1908 -1910 (Box Box 366)
  - Correspondence "L", including A. Leschen & Sons Rope Co.; C. W. Lee; Greenville Lewis Jr.; Theodore Low, 1905 -1908 (Box Box 366)
  - Correspondence "M", including N. D. Maher; Maryland Equipment & Supply Co.; McDermott Stone Co.; McSherry Mfg. Co.; Fritz Muller; H. Archer Mitchell; R. J. Kroyer, 1904 -1908 (Box Box 366)
  - Correspondence "N", including A. C. Needles; Newell-Morse Royalty Co.; W. S. Noble; Norfolk & Chesapeake Coal Co., 1905 -1908 (Box Box 366)
  - Orders, 1908 -1909 (Box Box 366)
  - Edward O'Toole, 1908 (Box Box 366)
  - Coal pamphlets, 1915 -1920 (Box Box 372)
  - Borderland Coal Co., 1920 (Box Box 372)
  - L. E. Armentrout - correspondence concerning labor problems, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 372)
  - Daily reports, 1916 -1917; (2 folders) (Box Box 373)
  - James P. Woods - correspondence, 1904 -1908 (Box Box 374)
  - Correspondence, including Louis A. Scholz, Sydney G. Stevens, W. C. Stephenson, Southern Fuel Co.; Southern West Virginia Fuel Co., J. J. Sullivan, Trenton Iron Works, Joseph Tipton, Walnut Hills Coal & Mining Co., H. W. Weiss, West Virginia Mine Supply, 1907 (Box Box 374)
  - Ernest B. Fishburn, Secretary-Treasurer of Borderland Coal Co., 1904 -1906 (Box Box 375)
  - Correspondence, including Buffalo Collieries Co., F. C. Bryan, Broderick & Bascom Rope Co., R. M. Bibb, W. C. Atwater, J. K. Anderson, J. K. Andrews & Co., Borderland Coal Co., E. B. Fishburn, 1904 -1908 (Box Box 375)
  - Correspondence, including John T. Alley, S. S. Cofer, John Fitzgerald, Judge F. H. Evans, E. C. Dame, "C" miscellaneous, F. W. Craig, Robert C. Crowthers, Consolidated Fuel Co., J. B Conners, Coals of the Coal River Basin Carl B. Clark, Charles S. Churchill, Cassidy Coal Co., Calder & Johnson, E. T. Burnett, 1905 -1908 (Box Box 375)
  - American Contractors Corp., 1905 -1910 (Box Box 375)
  - E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., including daily reports, 1911 -1917; (3 folders) (Box Box 376)
  - Correspondence, including Roberts & Bishop Insurance Agency, R. H. Rogers, A. D. Rice, Robins conveying Belt Co., H. K. Porter Co., Miscellaneous "P'' Charles G. Popp, Clarence R. Pope, Pocahontas Co., 1903 -1905 (Box Box 376)
  - D. E. Spangler, 1905 -1908 (Box Box 376)
  - Statements, 1905 -1909 (Box Box 376)
  - Blue prints - E. R. Johnson Mining Co., no date; (2 folders) (Box Box 378)
  - L. E. Armentrout - manager of E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., 1912 -1917 (Box Box 378)
  - James P. Woods - correspondence involving, Borderland Coal litigation. Woods is president of Borderland Coal and also a member of House of Representatives at Washington, D. C., 1918 -1919 (Box Box 388)
  - Statements from E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., 1909 -1914 (Box Box 390)
  - Scott & Buchanan - attorneys handling the selling of Borderland Coal stock, 1917 (Box Box 390)
  - J. H. Sluss - president and treasurer of E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., 1912 (Box Box 390)
  - J. P. Small - superintendent of E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., 1913 -1917 (Box Box 390)
  - James P. Woods, 1913 -1916 (Box Box 390)
  - West Virginia Standard Coal Co., 1916 -1917 (Box Box 390)
  - Monthly reports from E. R. Johnson Coal Mine, 1909 -1910 (Box Box 390)
  - Correspondence, including The Gravity Measuring Coal Chute Co., The Jeffrey Mfg. Co., Income Tax Dept. of the U.S. Government, 1911 -1914 (Box Box 391)
  - Mining leases, 1906 -1912 (Box Box 391)
  - Inventory of stock of merchandise in Borderland Coal storehouse, 1912 -1915 (Box Box 391)
  - Fuel contracts and related correspondence, 1913 -1917 (Box Box 409)
  - Monthly balance sheets for Borderland Operations 1 and 2, 1915 May -1916 Nov. (Box Box 409)
  - Borderland Coal Sales Co. - minutes, letters, statements, and balance sheets, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 409)
  - Coal Age Magazine - circulars promoting books on coal industry, 1914 -1917 (Box Box 409)
  - Borderland Coal blueprints of seams in Borderland mines, no date; (2 folders) (Box Box 412)
  - James P. Woods - president of Borderland Coal, 1915 -1917; (2 folders) (Box Box 419)
  - Borderland Coal Co. statements, 1913 -1917 (Box Box 419)
  - Vulcan Coal Co., 1915 -1917 (Box Box 419)
  - Public Service Commission, 1916 (Box Box 419)
  - Borderland Coal correspondence, 1917 (Box Box 419)
  - National Manufacturing Association, 1911 (Box Box 419)
  - Plant #2 orders - orders for coal; do not show prices; separated by plant number after April 1911, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 429)
  - Plant #1 orders, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 429)
  - Orders, 1909 July -1911 March; (2 folders) (Box Box 429)
  - Borderland Coal miscellaneous letters, 1912 (Box Box 430)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "L", including loading cars; list of houses (with size and costs); Lowe property and lease; League for Industrial Rights; M. S. Lambert - cashier, 1908 -1922 (Box Box 436)
  - Leases, agreements, and reports on property relevant to Borderland Coal, 1928 (Box Box 436)
  - Monthly operation #1 - output figures and costs, 1914 -1918 (Box Box 436)
  - Monthly operation #2, 1914 -1918 (Box Box 436)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", including G. S. Moore, Supt. of Transportation; Mining Rules; W. E. Mingea; Memorandum of Agreement; Memorandum and Notes, 1910 -1924 (Box Box 436)
  - Plant #1 - Borderland - purchase orders for supplies for coal plant in Borderland, Mingo County, 1914 Feb. -1915 June (Box Box 445)
  - Plant #2 - Armen - purchase orders for coal plant in Armen, Mingo County, 1914 -1915 June (Box Box 445)
  - Tariffs - freight rates for shipping coal, 1904 -1909 (Box Box 445)
  - E. A. Blake - Portsmouth, Ohio - siding for Borderland Coal, 1909 -1910 (Box Box 446)
  - Blackmer Rotary Pump - advertising brochures, no date (Box Box 446)
  - Borderland Coal: seam blueprints, 1915 (Box Box 446)
  - Blueprints - new coaling station, no date (Box Box 446)
  - #1 Mine, Winifrede Seam - blueprint, 1915 March (Box Box 446)
  - Borderland Coal: composite financial records, 1898 -1932 (Box Box 451)
  - Borderland Coal: statistics on coal production and revenue, 1904 -1912 (Box Box 453)
  - Borderland Coal: tonnage statements by month, 1919 Nov. -1922 Dec. (Box Box 453)
  - Borderland Coal: inventories of company stores, 1915 Dec., 1918 June -July, 1919 June, Dec. (Box Box 453)
  - Borderland Coal: requisitions, 1922 Oct. -1923 March, 1924 Aug. -1926 Aug. (Box Box 453)
  - Prices: Borderland Coal Co. and Pocahontas Field, 1917 -1919 (Box Box 453)
  - Reports on property, 1903 March -1907 Aug. (Box Box 453)
  - Borderland Coal: pay roll, 1905 Jan. (Box Box 453)
  - Operation sheet: Borderland Coal Sales Co., 1920 Jan. -1921 March (Box Box 453)
  - Borderland Coal: production costs, 1927 (Box Box 453)
  - Catalogue of Goodman Mfg. Co., 1916 Oct. (Box Box 454)
  - United States Fuel Administration, 1918 March -July (Box Box 454)
  - Contracts with Virginia Bridge & Iron Co, 1921 May -1922 Jan. (Box Box 454)
  - Borderland Coal: taxes, 1919 Dec. -1933 Dec.; (4 folders) (Box Box 454)
  - Borderland Coal: insurance, 1919 Dec. -1920 Feb. (Box Box 454)
  - Contents of safe deposit box and Stone's letter relinquishing keys, 1933 Dec. (Box Box 454)
  - Letter to users about Borderland Sales Co. going out of business, 1928 May (Box Box 454)
  - Photograph, no date (Box Box 454)
  - Miscellaneous, including pamphlets on Herrin Coal Mine Massacre, Southern Business Conditions - 1928, no date, 1916 June (Box Box 454)
  - Coal-related newspaper clippings, 1925 April, 1928 Feb. -May (Box Box 454)
  - Employer/Employee relations, 1922 Feb. (Box Box 455)
  - Workmen's Compensation Law, 1918 March -1919 (Box Box 455)
  - Kentucky Washroom Bill, 1920 April (Box Box 455)
  - Unions, 1920 Oct. -1921 Oct. (Box Box 455)
  - Labor conditions in Williamson Field - statement of Harry Olmstead, Chairman of the Labor Committee of the Operators' Assoc. of Williamson Field to the (United States) Senate Investigating Committee, 1921 July (Box Box 455)
  - Operators Assoc. of Williamson Field, 1902-1933; (2 folders) (Box Box 455)
  - Contract with Appalachian Coals, Inc., 1933 May (Box Box 455)
  - Correspondence and Related Material, 1923-1935; (7 folders) (Box Box 457)
  - Contract with Jeffrey Manufacturing Co., 1912 Jan 2 (Box Box 460)
  - Agreement with Appalachian Coals, 1932 Jan 20 (Box Box 460)
  - Coal-related Newsclippings, 1933 Sep 17 (Box Box 460)
  - Bulletin: "Norfolk and Western Railway Co., Coal Car Distribution Bulletin #85", ca. 1925 (Box Oversize)
  - Map: "New Map and Mine Directory of the Norfolk & Western Railway - Reduced Facsimile of 1910 Edition" (Box Oversize)
  - Map: "Thacker Seam, Borderland Coal Corp.. ." (Box Oversize)
  - Map: Parts of West Virginia and Kentucky (Box Oversize)
  - Quarterly Progress Sheets for Borderland Coal Corp., Thacker Seam Mines, ca. 1925 -1926 (Box Oversize)
  - Middle Seam Maps
    All items listed below are blueprints.
    - 1. "Map of Mine Workings... Middle Seam--Operation No. 1 -- Pike County -- Kentucky," 1915 January 1-1916 October. Scale 1"=100' (Box Oversize)
    - 2. "Map of Mine Workings... Middle Seam--Operation No. 1 -- Pike County -- Kentucky," 1915 January 1-1917 March 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 3. "Map of Mine Workings... Middle Seam--Operation No. 1 -- Pike County -- Kentucky," 1915 January 1-1917 June 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 4. "Map of Mine Workings... Middle Seam--Operation No. 1 -- Pike County -- Kentucky," 1915 January 1-1917 September 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 5. "Map of Mine Workings... Middle Seam--Operation No. 1 -- Pike County -- Kentucky," 1915 December 1-1917 May 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 6. "Operation No. 2 Middle Seam Pike Co., Ky." 1915 December 1-1916 December 1. Scale 1"=100' (Box Oversize)
    - 7. "Operation No. 2 Middle Seam Pike Co., Ky." 1915 December 1-1917 March 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 8. "Operation No. 2 Middle Seam Pike Co., Ky." 1915 December 1-1917 September 1 (Box Oversize)
  - Winifrede Seam Maps
    - 1. "Operation No. 1, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1914 September 1-1916 November 1. Scale: 1"-100' (Box Oversize)
    - 2. "Operation No. 1, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1914 September 1-1917 March (Box Oversize)
    - 3. "Operation No. 1, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1914 September 1-1917 June 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 4. "Operation No. 1, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1914 September 1-1917 August 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 5. "Operation No. 2, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1915 April 1-1917 March. Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
    - 6. "Operation No. 2, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1915 April 1-1917 September 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 7. "Operation No. 2, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1915 April 1-1916 December 1 (Box Oversize)
    - 8. "Operation No. 2, Winifrede Seam. Pike Co., Ky." 1915 April 1-1917 May 1 (Box Oversize)
  - Maps "Accompanying Report of March 13, 1917"
    - 1. "Operation No. 2 Middle Seam Pike Co., Ky." 1915 December 1- 1917 March 1. Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
    - 2. "Map Showing Property Lines, Outcrop, and Mine Development of Thacker Seam at Operation No.'s [sic] 1 & 2. Borderland, W.Va. July 15, 1915." Scale: 1" = 500' (Box Oversize)
    - 3."Map Showing Property Lines, Outcrop, and Mine Development of Winifrede Seam at Operations No.'s 1 & 2... ." Scale: 1" = 500' (Box Oversize)
    - 4. "Map Showing Property Lines, Outcrop, and Mine Development of Mid-Seam at Operations No.'s 1 & 2... ." Scale: 1" = 500' (Box Oversize)
    - 5. "Map of Mine Workings... Middle Seam--Peration No. 1--Pike County--Kentucky." 1915 January 1 - 1917 March. Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
    - 6. "Operations No 2 Winifrede Seam Pike Co., Ky." 1915 April 1-1917 March .1 Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
    - 7. "Map of Mine Workings... Thacker Seam--Operation No. 2 Pike County--Kentucky" 1912 December 1-1916 February 1. Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
    - 8. "Operation No. 1 Winifrede Seam Pike Co., Ky." 1914 September 1-1917 March 1. Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
    - 9. "Map of Plant... Operation No. 1 Borderland, W.Va." Coats & Burchard Co. Public Appraisers & Engineers, Chicago, 1916 November 1. Scale: 1" = 100' (Box Oversize)
- Stone Printing and Manufacturing Company Papers
  - Stone Printing: Mergenthaler Linotype Co., 1920 Sept. -1934 Sept. (Box Box 11)
  - Correspondence with J. R. McConnell of Randolph and Cumberland Railroad, 1914 Jan. -March (Box Box 11)
  - Correspondence, 1936 Aug. -Oct. (Box Box 11)
  - Newspaper, 1935 Aug. (Box Box 11)
  - Stone Printing: company advertisements, 1920 Nov. -1932, no date; (5 folders) (Box Box 14)
  - UTA letters, 1923 June -1931 Dec.; (4 folders) (Box Box 26)
  - UTA New Orleans Convention, including guest lists, correspondence, seating arrangements and menus for Oct. 1931 convention of United Typothetae Assoc., 1931 May -Oct., no date (Box Box 26)
  - 160 samples: fine print samples, no date; (2 folders) (Box Box 26)
  - J. Blair Farrar, including communication with accounting firm for Stone Printing, miscellaneous reports, papers, notes with no dates, 1903 -1906; (6 folders) (Box Box 38)
  - Memos and copy - sketches and proofs for ads made by Stone Printing, no date; (2 folders) (Box Box 39)
  - Samples of office forms - manufactured by Stone Printing, no date (Box Box 39)
  - E. Lawrence Fell - Stone's correspondence with a printing associate, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 39)
  - Franklin Monthly - copies of newsletter of Ben Franklin club, 1909 (Box Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous "F" - office forms, no date (Box Box 39)
  - Franklin Printing Co. - correspondence, 1911 (Box Box 39)
  - Albert W. Finlay, George H. Ellis Co. - cost accounting matters of Stone Printing, 1911 -1914 (Box Box 39)
  - Typothetae of Central and Western Virginia - Stone's correspondence, as head of Stone Printing, with this professional association, 1930 -1931 (Box Box 41)
  - Memos and copy "A-H" - sketches and ideas for ads, alphabetized by client's name, no date (Box Box 42)
  - Memos and copy "J-Z", no date (Box Box 42)
  - Correspondence, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 50)
  - Stone Printing and reaction to NRA correspondence, 1933, 1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 53)
  - Newspaper clippings on NRA, 1933, 1934 (Box Box 53)
  - Chamber of Commerce and the NRA, 1933 (Box Box 53)
  - Tariff page experiment - correspondence, 1911 -1913 March; (4 folders) (Box Box 62)
  - Time sheets for type setting on tariff page, 1913 (Box Box 62)
  - Proofs - Tariff Page Experiment, 1913 (Box Box 62)
  - Order memos and printing proofs "A-M", 1913 (Box Box 64)
  - Order memos and printing proofs "N-Z", 1913 (Box Box 64)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts -newsletters, 1929 -1931 (Box Box 72)
  - Typographia--- printing correspondence and printed material, 1921 -1925; (2 folders) (Box Box 72)
  - William Edwin Rudge - correspondence with owner of large New York printing company, 1922 -1930; (3 folders) (Box Box 72)
  - Tariff Printers Society - correspondence and printed material, 1923 -1925; (3 folders) (Box Box 78)
  - Henry P. Porter - Boston, Mass. printing correspondence, 1920 -1935 (Box Box 78)
  - Charles E. Stone - correspondence, 1929 -1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 81)
  - N.R.A. - correspondence and printed material concerning Stone's opposition to the Wagner Act, 1933 -1935 (Box Box 82)
  - President's Camp Booklet - concerns Hoover's presidential retreat on the Rapidan River in the Blue Ridge Mountains done by Stone Printing; contains correspondence concerning the booklet and also the text for the booklet, 1931; (5 folders) (Box Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous, memos, etc., 1932 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 83)
  - United Typothetae of America - an international association of master printers in which Stone is an active member; contain pamphlets, publication on its labor policy, correspondence, etc., 1921 -1926; (3 folders) (Box Box 87)
  - Stone miscellaneous correspondence, 1922; (2 folders) (Box Box 87)
  - Printers' Board of Trade - Philadelphia, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 87)
  - Albert A. Stone - president and treasurer of Stone Printing & Mfg. Co., 1920 -1923 (Box Box 88)
  - T. J. Lyon, Byrd Printing Co., including material concerning the Southern Printers' Society, 1911 (Box Box 89)
  - Kohn & Pollock - printing correspondence, 1912 (Box Box 89)
  - John A. Hutton, Braid & Hutton, 1912 (Box Box 89)
  - H. H. Hughs, John P. Morton & Co., 1912 (Box Box 89)
  - E. D. Hotchkiss, 1909 -1914 (Box Box 89)
  - General Tariff Assoc., John A. Henderson, Washington, D.C., 1913 (Box Box 89)
  - Lambert-Deacon-Hull Printing Co., 1913 -1918 (Box Box 89)
  - J. P. Denham, Daggett Printing Co., 1912 (Box Box 89)
  - C. Med. Davis, Ass't. General, Freight Agent Atlantic Coast Line, 1911 (Box Box 89)
  - Crane & Co., 1910 (Box Box 89)
  - Coupon tickets, 1909 (Box Box 89)
  - W. H. Cogswell, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 89)
  - A. C. Balch, J. B. Lippincott Co., 1911 (Box Box 89)
  - A. G. Brandau of Brandau-Craig-Dickerson Co., 1916 -1921 (Box Box 89)
  - E. T. Burnett & T. S. Davant, 1916 -1917 (Box Box 89)
  - Winston-Salem Southbound Railway Co., 1911 (Box Box 89)
  - Frank P. Allen, 1910 (Box Box 89)
  - Associated Railway of Va. and the Carolinas, 1913 (Box Box 89)
  - Advertisements related to printing, 1917 -1925 (Box Box 90)
  - Financial records, 1923 -1930, 1909 (Box Box 90)
  - Business publications, 1932 (Box Box 90)
  - Stone Printing correspondence, 1920 -1935 (Box Box 90)
  - Applications for work at Stone Printing during early part of the depression, 1930 -1933 (Box Box 94)
  - United Typothetae of America - printing correspondence, 1927 -1929; (2 folders) (Box Box 95)
  - Forth District Typothetae - printing correspondence, 1920 -1929; (2 folders) (Box Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous "H", 1912 (Box Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous "I, K", 1910 -1911 (Box Box 109)
  - Lanston Monotype Machinery Co., 1908 -1911 (Box Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous "L", 1908 (Box Box 109)
  - H. W. J. Meyer Printing Co., 1910 -1917 (Box Box 109)
  - Costs: The Master Printer, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", 1910 -1911 (Box Box 109)
  - Printing costs - notes and memos, 1911 (Box Box 109)
  - Publications costs - correspondence and estimates, 1908 -1911 (Box Box 109)
  - Purse Printing Co., 1911 -1915 (Box Box 109)
  - American Printers Cost Commission System - instructions, time sheets, computation tables, ca. 1910 (Box Box 112)
  - Printing costs "A" - booklets, correspondence, and advice about efficiency and costs, 1911 (Box Box 112)
  - Printing costs and miscellaneous "B", 1911 -1912 (Box Box 112)
  - Printing costs "C", 1909 -1912 (Box Box 112)
  - Printing costs "D", 1909 -1912 (Box Box 112)
  - Printing costs "E", 1909 -1912 (Box Box 112)
  - R. A. Hughes - correspondence, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "L", 1909 -1912 (Box Box 113)
  - Harris, N. W. & Co. - concerning electricity for Stone Printing, 1909 -1912 (Box Box 113)
  - Offset presses - inquiries, catalogues about offset presses, correspondence, 1909 -1910 (Box Box 113)
  - Patents - copies of and description circulars about a printing press Stone invented, 1907 (Box Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "P", 1911 (Box Box 113)
  - Presses "A" - samples, catalogues, and letters from printing press manufacturers, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 114)
  - Presses "B, C", 1930 -1915 (Box Box 114)
  - Presses "D", 1910 -1915 (Box Box 114)
  - Presses "S", 1910 -1915 (Box Box 114)
  - Presses "T-W", 1910 -1915 (Box Box 114)
  - UT & FCA (United Typothetae & Franklin Club of America), 1915 -1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 120)
  - United Typothetae and Franklin Clubs of America - membership lists, minutes and financial records, 1913 -1916; (3 folders) (Box Box 121)
  - Prices and samples of Stone Printing products, 1908 (Box Box 126)
  - Photographic contest - entries and winners in the contest, managed by Stone Printing, 1912 (Box Box 126)
  - John A. Pilcher - correspondence between Stone Printing and Norfolk & Western, 1916 (Box Box 126)
  - A. J. Brandau - correspondence about tariff printing and printing costs, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 128)
  - Jo E. Burke - Burke & Gregory - correspondence between Stone Printing and this Norfolk Typesetting Co., 1910 -1913 (Box Box 128)